Hello everyone, Eishiro Sugata here once again.
This here is my assistant, Pretty II.
Isn't she lovely?
515 years ago, in the year 1494,
on June 7th, the countries of Portugal and Spain signed the Treaty of Tordesillas.
In 1529, they signed the Treaty of Saragossa.
This allowed the great powers of the day to effectively split the world into different regions,
much like the pattern on a watermelon.
This practice is called demarcation.
This demarcation is illustrated here on the watermelon, showing how the world was divided up.
We could even call this fruit a figurehead for the new world.
Inside of this ancient concept, we should be able to find clues to the new world.
It's very wise to not take a watermelon lightly.
I can hear my heart pain.
this world isn't different too.
This is where they plan to find clues.
The first time was the time of antes.
Thank you.
Do you hear me?
Well, good for you, Tomaki.
But hold on a sec.
I still don't even understand what the question is asking.
Do you have the slightest clue?
You're not the smartest girl I know.
If I couldn't figure it out, you don't have a chance in hell.
Get real.
What a pain in my ass.
Oh, I know.
Why don't I get Icarus to give me another card?
No way!
Everyone in the world will be pissed at you if more craft blows up in our faces!
I thought it was a good idea.
You've got to take this seriously.
You think you'll ever get your homework done if you keep rolling around on the floor like that?
You won't.
Are you listening?
Yeah, I was just calculating the area of the triangle that's made from the way you were sitting.
If you have the face, time to hide the...
This sucks.
We won't get any work done if you keep screwing around.
I got it!
Sugata could help teach us some math.
He's a real smart guy.
Yes, you are certainly at the Sugata house, but there's no boy named Eiichiro living here.
Sorry.
That's weird.
This is the only house around here that's got the Sugata name on the door.
And since we can't raise him on his cell phone either, I guess we're SOL.
Well, if it isn't Zohara and Tomoki.
Oh, hi, Prez.
Yo, how's it hanging? Good to see you.
You two out on a hot day.
Oh, hell no!
Okay.
But surely the two of you are close enough now that you can bathe together, right?
What is wrong with you?
I heard a little rumor recently.
I heard Tomoki picks out all of your underwear for you.
Is that true?
No.
Of course it's not.
Wasn't it just the other day, though, when you had her handcuffed after forcibly removing her panties?
That... that was an accident!
Anyway, it looks to me like the two of you are trying to find Sugata's place.
If you knew that to begin with, why the hell are you messing with our heads?
You'll need to head down to the riverbank.
Would you be opposed to having me show you the way?
The riverbank?
This is it?
This flimsy tent is where you live?
Yeah.
What's the problem?
You go back and forth from here to school every day.
That's a heck of a commute.
That it is.
Welcome to my humble abode.
Thanks for having us.
But of course, it's my pleasure.
This is it?
This flimsy tent is where you live?
Yeah, what's the problem?
You go back and forth from here to school every day.
That's a heck of a commute.
That it is.
Welcome to my humble abode.
Thanks for having us.
But of course, it's my pleasure.
Question 3, Part 1, Identities.
Cosine of x plus sine of i minus 5 equals the cosine of 5.
The first thing we'll do is expand the equation on the left side of the equals sign.
If you do that, you get...
A problem that's fairly simple to solve, don't you think?
No kidding.
If this guy's going to pretend to be a mathematician,
he should at least try dishing out some harder equations.
Yeah, he's on a whole other level.
What's the matter? Is it too hard?
Hey, yo!
Icarus, you think you could knock out the rest of this equation for me?
An equation?
I'll try.
I don't get it.
Why'd you give it to her?
You should recall, she said before that she was created, didn't she?
I am a pet class, Angeloid.
Icarus.
I was manufactured by the Synapse.
Oh yeah, she did say that.
Basically, if she's really a robot or something like it,
my assumption is she should have superior computational abilities.
Equation complete.
That was fast!
Kick ass!
So there was no reason to even bother coming out of here in the first place!
Ha ha ha ha!
Huh?
I guess I'll do the rest of the equation myself.
I'd really appreciate it.
Man, I was all excited and then you just wrote master on every page and in pin!
I gotta turn that in tomorrow!
She lacks computational abilities, but that shouldn't be the case.
Finally, we're finished.
Excellent work, you guys.
If you don't mind, a cold drink would be great right now.
No problem.
I'll get it for you, Prez.
Thank you so much for your help, Sugata.
It was nothing.
I'm happy to help you guys.
Why don't you let us do something as a way to say thanks?
And we won't take no for an answer.
Oh, I'm getting something in return.
Huh?
Look at this.
It's that black hole thing you showed us.
That computer model shows the disturbances still in the airspace above the city.
Up to this point, the New World has basically been circumnavigating the Earth.
But currently, it's holding its position above the city.
This sort of thing has never happened before.
All I see when I look up is the beautiful sky.
When I saw it the night I found Icarus, it was like this ginormous dark hole ripped through the sky.
Maybe it's refracting light somehow or hiding behind the clouds.
Its whole nature remains a mystery to us as of now.
Yo, Icarus, do me a favor.
Fly up and check out the black hole for us.
As you wish, Master.
I didn't find anything out of the ordinary, Master.
If she can't find a problem, there must not be anything screwy going on.
She's got to be covering for something.
You look like that bothers you.
What's up?
Uh, I'm fine.
Just want to confirm a few things for myself.
Sorry to say it might take some time.
It's something I'm going to have to do alone.
Hmm?
You're planning on flying up there yourself?
Uh, yeah.
I'm going to run another test flight tomorrow.
And I'd like the two of you to help me out if you wouldn't mind.
I mean, you have tomorrow off from school.
Why don't you stay out here tonight?
What?
One, two, pull.
Looks like Sugata and I will be the ones stuck with making the food for everyone.
Tomoki and Sahara will be catching the fish for dinner.
And Icarus will go out to do the rest of the shopping.
She's going to do our shopping?
I don't think that's the best idea in the world.
I disagree.
It might be a good opportunity.
Give her various tasks and you'll find out, I think, just how powerful she really is.
I'm right to say you still don't know about most of her abilities, yes?
Well, yeah, but...
Then consider this an opportunity for you to learn something.
I smell an adventure!
You're not helping, Sahara.
She'll never survive out there.
She'll be fine on her own.
The people in this town are nice almost to a fault.
They'll help her with whatever she needs.
Okay, Icarus, listen up.
This is important.
You need to run some errands.
And I want you to act like a normal person.
Think you can do it?
Of course, Master.
Wait!
Curry!
Before you go, you need to have money and you need to figure out what it is you're picking
up.
Of course, Master.
We're having curry tonight.
Now I'm putting the list right here in your bag.
Goodbye, then.
I'll be back soon.
Stop!
Do you know any normal humans who fly when they're running errands?
I do.
Shut up!
You do not!
I do not.
How are you doing today?
Um, can I help you?
If you like it that much, I'll give it to you at a discount.
I just followed her because I was worried.
Now I can't even tell what she's up to.
Hmm.
Seems she finds something interesting.
What the hell are you doing here?
I guess we were all kind of worried about her.
I admit I am curious as to whether she'll get the ingredients we need.
Hush.
She might just hear us.
Look!
She's picking out the vegetables.
I must get carrots.
And potatoes.
And onions.
Oh, so close.
That wasn't close at all.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure she bought the watermelon.
This is an intriguing phenomenon.
All she has to buy now is meat.
This is where it really counts.
Curry isn't curry without meat.
I won't stand for anything called curry without at least some kind of meat.
Now, I must get meat.
Everybody, spectacular and curry sounds awesome!
I have no problem whatsoever with deboning a chick.
Watermelon.
Carrots.
Potatoes.
Onions.
Meat.
Baby chicken curry.
You can't kill it!
No!
I almost forgot.
The base for the curry.
I don't think you make curry with soy sauce.
Master, did I not shop correctly for meal preparation?
You get an F for shopping.
You're going to need a hell of a lot more practice.
I'm sorry, Master.
I guess for your first time, you didn't do so bad.
Really.
Good job, Bicarious.
Yeah, don't worry, Mom.
I'm here with everyone else, so I'll be safe.
See you tomorrow.
Oh, check it.
I caught one.
Tomo.
Oh, yeah.
That's excellent.
Holy crap, you gotta help.
What do I do with...
My God, I'm so wet.
Hey, Tomoki?
What do you want?
I can't find Icarus.
Any idea where she is?
For playing out loud.
Where did that dumb girl run off to?
Hey!
Icarus!
Stop yelling.
I hear something.
What the hell was that?
Some kind of shockwave.
We got another one coming.
Hit the deck!
What is that thing on her back?
A pirarucu lives in the rivers of South America.
It is the world's largest freshwater fish.
Like the Amazon?
How did you get all the way there and back so quick?
I have the ability to fly at an airspeed of Mach 24.
Moving to Mach 24, considering other variables,
that's 30,000 kilometers per hour.
Well, since she brought it all the way here,
let's clean that fish, too.
It'd make a great side dish.
I wonder if something like that is even edible.
All right, Sagada.
What's got your panties in a twist?
Well, Mikiko...
These are the specs on Icarus.
That's correct.
Her maximum speed is...
Kind of a waste, isn't it?
An angel with seemingly unlimited power.
I mean, she's faster than the world's top fighter jets.
But she calls herself pet class.
Give me a break.
Let's eat!
Killers!
You actually made some real curry!
Shocking as it may sound, Icarus made it.
That's awesome.
You tried your best and it really shows, too.
Thanks a lot.
This is the best.
It's just like Mom used to make.
Beautiful.
The sweetness...
Hold up.
It's just meat and potatoes.
And I think I taste sugar.
It doesn't make any difference.
Meat and potatoes are the basic ingredients of curry, right?
No, I'm pretty sure that's curry.
Yeah, it wasn't that funny, Sahara.
I know, sorry.
It's just, ever since Icarus showed up, it seems like there's always something to laugh at.
I guess she didn't do this to our dinner on purpose.
Pardon?
Master?
I am curious as to what you were laughing at.
What do you mean?
We're just laughing to have a good time.
Isn't that reason enough?
Having a good time?
You mean, like fun?
Nothing out of the ordinary.
What are you, really?
If you didn't hear me, I'm asking you what you are.
I am a pet class Angeloid, type Alpha.
Don't play dumb with me.
Would anything that's just a pet have the need to, or be designed to, catch a gigantic fish alive,
or fly at Mach 24, but at the same time, your computational ability is that of a baby.
It also seems that your emotions are limited.
Both completely perfect and completely imperfect.
Just what are you?
Answer me.
Why have you sought out Tomoki?
There has to be a reason.
I do not know.
I am unaware of what my purpose should be on this world.
What do you mean?
I stay by his side.
Those are the orders Master gave me, and that is the only reason I have for remaining here with him.
But in doing so, I am constantly causing him great distress, and I do not know how to make that stop.
Much like how Master is angry with me right now, I am sure you have noticed this.
I can't help but wonder if I were to leave Master's side.
Maybe he would be better off.
She doesn't have the first clue what she is any more than I do.
So the problem becomes a question.
Who sent Icarus to Tomoki?
You should just do your best to have fun.
Hmm?
You should just do what you can to have a good time while you're around Tomoki.
And then you pray that the day you two part never comes.
Wind check, positioning check, weather conditions good.
Now hit the sky, Tomoki!
Aren't you the one supposed to be doing this insanity?
Everything's an experience.
Now go!
Take off!
You're a demon!
You're a devil incarnate!
Say if you will, this is repayment for all the homework help.
Tomoki, don't let go!
A fall like that will take him weeks to recover from.
I guess my calculations are still a tad off, which means that...
Pardon me.
May I ask you a question?
What is it?
You see, I was just wondering if...
if my Master's Master has fun when he is around Master.
Hmm?
I've been trying, but I still don't think I really understand what this word called fun means.
But I guess...
But what?
When I am with Master...
My heart feels lighter.
Like it's trying to fly right out of my chest all on its own.
That makes sense.
Then you should make that your homework assignment.
And I will expect you to turn in a report to me in one day.
Understood.
I'm back.
And I'm exhausted.
I'm glad you walked away from that fall with just cuts and bruises.
You brought the watermelon back with you?
Correct.
Well, in that case, I suppose we should have some.
You really like that watermelon, don't you?
At least our homework's done.
Yeah, and our impromptu camping trip was a whole lot of fun, too.
It gets funnier every time I look at it.
Tell me, Master.
Do you have a good time when I am here with you?
Boy, do I ever, Icarus.
There's never a dull moment with you around, that's for sure.
But before we get started tonight, folks, I've got a question.
What's the deal with these new HDTVs?
What are you scribbling on over there, Icarus?
I am writing on my homework.
And now we're going to be broadcasting in all digital formats,
which means you're going to get a technical question.
In high depth, in your home.
I see myself every day.
The stupid screws are loose.
Would you stop messing with the toilet seat?
Next time, Love and Triangles Revisited.